{
    "subject": "resource/Gerald_Maxwell",
    "predicate": "ontology/militaryUnit",
    "object": "resource/Lovat_Scouts",
    "human_readable": "Gerald Maxwell was part of the Lovat Scouts.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8639028668403625,
            "question": "Who was Gerald Maxwell part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5771610736846924,
            "question": "What group did Gerald Maxwell belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5618410110473633,
            "question": "To which organization did Gerald Maxwell belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5495897531509399,
            "question": "Was Gerald Maxwell involved in any notable historical events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.509306788444519,
            "question": "What was the purpose of the Lovat Scouts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4787527918815613,
            "question": "What is the Lovat Scouts known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4327702820301056,
            "question": "Are there any famous individuals associated with the Lovat Scouts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37854647636413574,
            "question": "What was the name of the military unit Gerald Maxwell was a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33691319823265076,
            "question": "Gerald Maxwell's affiliation was with what type of unit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2087750881910324,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Gerald Maxwell's military service?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gerald Maxwell was part of the Lovat Scouts.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5996_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gerald Maxwell's affiliation was with what type of unit?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5996_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the military unit Gerald Maxwell was a member of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5996_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous individuals associated with the Lovat Scouts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5996_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5996_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can answer your query as follows:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple references to Lord Lovat's nephew, Gerald Joseph Constable Maxwell, being commissioned into the Lovat Scouts (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5996/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5996/re-ranker-msmarco/101.txt). Therefore, the information supports the triple that Gerald Maxwell was part of the Lovat Scouts."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Lord Lovat, the uncle of Gerald Joseph Constable Maxwell, was notable for raising the Lovat Scouts in the Boer War. This information supports the triple that Gerald Maxwell was part of the Lovat Scouts."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}